McConnell, John W. Additional Arbitration Files 5961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John W. McConnell Additional Arbitration Files
1942-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McConnell, John W.
5961
29.22 cubic feet
29.2 linear ft.
Case files.
Arbitration files from a variety of cases, primarily in the northeastern United States. Numerous firms and government agencies are represented; the majority of cases concern employees of the U.S. Postal Service.
3441117
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 22, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Biographical / Historical
John W. McConnell, labor arbitrator, professor of industrial and labor relations, and dean, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /3052: John W. McConnell Papers /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4163: William Foote Whyte Additional Papers /4297: ILR School Biography Files /4309: M. Gardner Clark Papers 5102: Emergency Board No. 129, Long Island Railroad and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Records 6047: Archives Information File
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Grievance arbitration -- United States -- Cases; Arbitrators, Industrial; McConnell, John Wilkinson, 1907-; United States Postal Service -- Officials and employees.; United States Postal Service -- Personnel management.; United States Postal Service -- Management.
3441117
- National War Labor Board Decisions: 1942-1944 (Box 1)
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    February-April 1942
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    May-June 1942
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    July 1942
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    August 1942
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    September-October 1942
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    November 1942 - January 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    February-March 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    February-January 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    April-May 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    June-July 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    August-September 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    October- November 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    December 1943
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    January - February 1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    March-April 1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    May- June 1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    July- August 1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    September- October1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    November 1944
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    December 1944
- National War Labor Board Decisions: 1945 and Arbitrations: 1973 (Box 2)
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    January - February 1945
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    March - April 1945
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    May- June 1945
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    July - August 1945
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    September - October 1945
  - National War Labor Board Decisions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    November - December 1945
  - Buffalo Teachers Federation Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Teachers Federation Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Teachers Federation Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Teachers Federation Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Oxford Paper Co. and United Paper Workers Association International Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Oxford Paper Co. and United Paper Workers Association International Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Matter Of Arbitration: Kendall Co. Fiber Products and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Arbitrations: 1975-1982 (Box 3)
  - Board Of Cooperation Educational Services and Oswego County Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board Of Cooperative Educational Services and Oswego County Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Boise Cascade Co. Paperboard Division and United Paperworkers International Union Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Civil Services Employees Association Inc. and Field Staff Association Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Civil Services Employees Association Inc. and Field Staff Association Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Thin Metals Co. and United Steelworkers Of America Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Seneca County and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Arbitration, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ITT Royal Electric Division and International Brotherhood Of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and Mary F. Hart, Grievant Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Friendship Central Schools and Friendship Faculty Association Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - University Of Mass. Amherst and American Federation Of State County Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - TransWorld Airlines and Lucy Blasi, Grievant Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - TransWorld Airlines and Lucy Blasi, Grievant Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - University Of Mass. Medical Center Worchester and American Federation Of State Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The State Of Connecticut and New England Health Care Employees Arbitration, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - East Greenwich Education Association and East Greenwich School Committee Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Timex Clock Company and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - RI. Department Of Corrections and R.I. Brotherhood Of Correctional Officers Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1976-1982 (Box 4)
  - Applied Design Co., Inc. and Sheet metal Workers International Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Balco Inc. and Thomas and Paul E. Leary Arbitration, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Beloit Co. Jones Division and United Electrical, Roads, and Machine Workers of America Arbitration, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Belknap Business Forms Inc. and International Of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Worker Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dairylea Cooperatives, Inc. and Teamsters Local 338 Arbitration, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ernest Contraction Co. and International Business Assoc. Of Bridges Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Falmouth School Committee and Falmouth Educators Association Arbitration, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent Of Schools and Peru Association Of Teachers Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent Of Schools and Peru Association Of Teachers Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kellogg Brush Manufacturing Co. and Directly Affiliated Labor Union Arbitration, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Newport School Committee and Teachers Association Of Newport Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Newport School Committee and Teachers Association Of Newport Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYS Electrical and Gas Co. and International Brotherhood Of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Onondaga Central School District and Onondaga Central Faculty Association Arbitration, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rome Cable Co. Cyrus Wire and Cable Company and Internal Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Tiverton School Committee and Tiverton Education Association Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Tiverton School Committee and Tiverton Education Association Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Tiverton School Committee and Tiverton Education Association Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Torrington Co. and United Automobiles Workers Arbitration, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The Real Paper Inc. and The Real Paper Employees Association Arbitration, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Real Paper Inc. and The Real Paper Employees Association Arbitration, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Arbitrations: 1975-1981 (Box 5)
  - The Penn Yan Central School District and Penn Yan Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Penn Yan Central School District and Penn Yan Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Corning City School District and Corning Teachers Association Arbitration, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Corning City School District and Corning Teachers Association Arbitration, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Corning City School District and Corning Teachers Association Arbitration, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Public Employment Relations Board Arbitrations, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Includes arbitrations in Watertown, Auburn, Poughkeepsie, and Towanda
  - Public Employment Relations Board Arbitrations, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Includes: Arbitrations in Watertown, and Auburn. Photo documents.
  - Public Employment Relations Board Arbitrations, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Public Employment Relations Board Arbitrations, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Includes: arbitrations in Watertown. Budget booklet.
  - Marcellus Central School District and Marcellus Faculty Association Arbitration, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Broome County and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mosey Corned Beef Co. and United Food and Commercial Workers Arbitration, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Beekmantown Central School District and Beekmantown Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dunham-Bush Inc. and International Ass. Of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cortland-Madison Board of Co-op Educational Services and Cortland-Madison BOCES Teachers Assoc. Arbitration, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Oneonta City School District and Oneonta Teachers Assoc. Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jamestown Board of Education and Jamestown Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jamestown Board of Education and Jamestown Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Carpenter Technology Corp. Carpenter Steel Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Carpenter Technology Corp. Carpenter Steel Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Arbitrations: 1977-1981 (Box 6)
  - Arlington School Committee and Arlington Education Ass. Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Department of State and Thaddeus A. Ripa, Grievant Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Department of State Foreign Service Grievance Board and Robert N. Allen, Grievant Arbitration, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Department of State Foreign Service Board and Robert N. Allen, Grievant Arbitration, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jarvis and Jarvis. Division of Standes Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Glocester School Committee and Glocester Association Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Airco Speer Carbon Graphite and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - University of MASS Amherst and AFSCE, Council 93 Local 1776 Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Oneonta Central School District and Oneonta Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Ripley Central School District and Ripley Education Association Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Department of State Foreign Service Grievance Board and John C. Fry, Grievant Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Department of State Foreign Service Grievance Board and John C. Fry, Grievant Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Farfrir Bearing, A Division of Textron and International Union, Arbitrations, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Arbitration with International Union, United Automobile Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America
  - Beloit Corporation, Jones Division and U.E.R. and M.W.A. Local 212 Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Includes: Floor Plans
  - Beloit Corp. Jones Division and United Paper Workers Union Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Booksmith Distributions Co. and District 65 Distributive Workers Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Edgecombe Metals Company and United Steelworkers of America Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - United States Postal Services and American Postal Service Union Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - United Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - United Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - United Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - United States Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - United States Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - United States Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - NYS Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Includes: Floor plans
- Arbitrations: 1977-1981 (Box 7)
  - Schweitzer Aircraft Corp. and International Union Arbitration, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Arbitration with International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America
  - Chenango Valley Central School District and Chenango Valley Teachers Association Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Horseheads Central School District and Horseheads Teachers Association, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Umass, Amherst and AFSCME Council 93 Arbitration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Umass, Amherst and AFSCME Council 93 Arbitration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - UMass, Amherst and AFSCME Council 93 Arbitration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gowanda Central School District and Gowanda Teachers Association Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Handy and Hardman Plant and United Steelworkers of America Arbitration., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Netti Wholesale Beverage Inc. and Brewery Workers Local 1149 Arbitration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Crown Zellerbach Corp. and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - City if Lackawanna, NY and Fire Dept. Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - St. Lawrence University and Service Employees International Union Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Field Staff Association and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Standard Shade Roller Division and UPIU Local 860 Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    UPIU-United Paper Workers International Union
  - Dundee Central School District and Dundee Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gates Chili Central School District Superintendent and Gates Chili Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital and New England Health Care Employees Union Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Includes: Maps
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Arbitrations: 1979-1982 (Box 8)
  - Honeoye Central School District and Honeoye Teachers Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Honeoye Central School District and Honeoye Teachers Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Honeoye Central School District and Honeoye Teachers Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - City of Buffalo Fire Dept. and Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - County of Albany and The Civil Service Employees Association Inc. Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Avoca Central School District and Avoca Teachers Association Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - N-L Industries Inc. and Joseph Benoit, Grievant Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Monroe County Water Authority and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Includes: Map of Distribution Serviceman Daytime Areas
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Includes: Posters and Photo documents
  - The Real Paper Inc. and The Real Paper Employees Association Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Philips ECG Inc. A Division of North American Philips Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and John McConnell, Grievant Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy Valve Division of ITT Grinnell Valve Co. Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Includes: Maps and Floor Plans
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Includes: Employee timecards
  - Mohawk Valley Community College and Mohawk Valley Community College Professional Association Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Includes: Photo documents and employee timecards
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and National Association for Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Potsdam Paper Corp. and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Service and America Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Includes: Mail cards
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Arbitrations: 1979-1982 (Box 9)
  - Union Problems And Requests, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Union Problems and Requests, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Arbitration between City Of Cohoes and Uniform Firefighters Of Cohoes
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1966-1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Union Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - McGraw Central School District and McGraw Central School Non-Instructional Employees (CSEA) Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - McGraw Central School District and McGraw Central School Non-Instructional Employees (CSEA) Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - McGraw Central School District and McGraw Central School Non-Instructional Employees (CSEA) Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Compulsory Interest Arbitration: The City of Niagara and Captains and Lieutenants, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Grievances, Requests, and Arbitrations, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Grievances, Requests, and Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Auburn Enlarged City School District Arbitrations, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Auburn Enlarged City School District Arbitrations, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Auburn Enlarged City School District Arbitrations, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1979-1982 (Box 10)
  - NYS Dept. Of Banking Rolando Galang and Public Employee Federation Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NYS Dept. Of Banking Rolando Galang and Public Employee Federation Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NYS Dept. of Banking Rolando Galang and Public Employees Federation Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - NYS Dept. of Banking Rolando Galang and Public Employees Federation Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - City of Syracuse and Police Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)